TYE HADFIELD

Software Developer

CONTACT

Address Brisbane, QLD, 4000

Phone 0466 753 998

E-mail tye_hadfield@hotmail.com

LinkedIn www.linkedin.com/in/tyehadfield

Twitter
https://twitter.com/Tyehadfield

GitHub https://github.com/Tye-Hadfield

TOOLS

Portfolio tyehadfield.tech

TECH STACK

CSS / HTML Git / Github
Ruby /Ruby on Rails VS Code
React Trello
Bootstrap Jira
JavaScript
PostgreSQL

EDUCATION

2020-08 - Current Diploma: Software Development Coder Academy - Brisbane

About Me

A passionate junior Software Developer with a fire to be better everyday! Experience with coding in Ruby/Rails and Javascript and a wide range of other development languages. Critical thinker who has been successful in previous software companies and award achieving customer relationship skills. Currently studying at Coder Academy with an end date of February 2021, I look forward to starting my journey back into the software industry in a new section.

Projects

OnlyTips (Horse Tips) - Two way marketplace

Tech Stack Tools
- Ruby / Ruby on rails
- CSS / HTML - JavaScript - Bootstrap

Github and hosted app
https://github.com/Tye-Hadfield/OnlyTips
https://immense-meadow-06650.herokuapp.com/

Pokedex and Safari - Terminal Application

Tech Stack Tools
- Ruby -Git/Github
- CSS / HTML -Vs Code
- Trello

Github

https://github.com/Tye-Hadfield/Pokedex_with_PokeSafari

Work History

02/2020 -Current

Support Worker

Self-Employed, Brisbane, QLD

- Promoted community integration by providing extensive physical, emotional and social support.
- Documented daily activities, behaviors and incidents for permanent record.
- Provided IT skills through small workshops and 1 on 1training.

11/2018 -08/2019

Tier II Support Analyst

iPipeline, Salt Lake City, Utah

- Provided answers to clients by identifying problems researching answers guiding clients through corrective steps.
- Completed necessary internal and client related documentation's required on a daily basis.
- Improved system performance by identifying problems recommending changes.
- Learned internal software solutions and provided customer training.

(Award) - Stickman award winner for perfect survey scores

2017-05 -2018-11

Help Desk Technician

iPipeline, Salt Lake City, Utah

- Assisted in testing of new functionality, enhancements to existing functionality and fixes to issues.
- Helped create, maintain and update procedure(s) documentation.
- Documented and escalated customer-identified bug reports and suggestions for product enhancements.